<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Shows on Gener8</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/shows/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Shows on Gener8</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/shows/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Environmental management</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/shows/shows/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/shows/shows/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Racktivity developed the &lt;a href=&#34;../products/uptime-maximization-opex-reduction/e2sensor&#34;&gt;E²Sensor&lt;/a&gt; Family to give you visibility of the environmental situation of your data centers and remote infrastructure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whether you are looking to monitor temperature, humidity, water leakage, movement, smoke detection or other parameters we have the E²Sensor available to fit your needs. The E²Sensor is designed to work with any Racktivity product featuring an R-BUS connector which includes the &lt;a href=&#34;../products/rack-power-management&#34;&gt;EnergySwitch smart PDUs&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;../products/infrastructure-power-management/ac-power-monitoring-ac2meter&#34;&gt;AC²Meter&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;../products/infrastructure-power-management/dc-power-monitoring&#34;&gt;DC²Meter&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The E²Sensor is a compact environmental sensor of 5cm (2 inches) that comes equipped with an OLED display.
Deployment is simple via the standard RJ45 daisy chain connections and features multiple rack mount options. A simple push button allows instant control of all available metrics such as temperature, humidity, leak detection, motion detection, rack door close sensor, smoke indication…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The sensors are fully compatible with our &lt;a href=&#34;../products/power-management-software/dcpm&#34;&gt;DCPM&lt;/a&gt;, a Service Provider Infrastructure &amp;amp; Data Center Performance Management System, allowing you a complete monitoring and management solution of critical environmental metrics in your data centers and/or smaller distributed infrastructures.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Want to find out where exactly the Racktivity products go in the datacenter? &lt;a href=&#34;../post/data-center-floor-plan-solution-overview&#34;&gt;Check out our animated floor plan.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>